<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--Link to stylesheet/XSLT-->
<?xml-stylesheet  href="test.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>

<store>
    <movie>
        <game>Call Of Duty: Black Ops III</game>
        <description>
        Call of Duty®: Black Ops III deploys its players into
        a future where biotechnology has enabled a new breed 
        of Black Ops soldier. Call of Duty: Black Ops III for
        PlayStation® 3 and Xbox 360 features two modes only: 
        Multiplayer and Zombies, providing fans with
        an expansive Multiplayer and an 
        all-new film-noir Zombies adventure. 9/10
              </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> Treyarch</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring> Smosh</starring>
            
        </casts>
        
        <price>‎‎Price € 59.99</price>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <game>FIFA 15</game>
        <description>
           FIFA 15 brings football to life in stunning detail so
            fans can experience the emotion of the sport like
           never before. Witness the intensity of crowds
         chanting and cheering like on match day, and listen to
         commentators guide fans through the story of the 
        game with Dynamic Match Presentation... 8/10

        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> EA</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
           <starring>John</starring>
        </casts>
       
        <price>‎Price € 39.99</price>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <game>Minecraft</game>
        <description>
           Minecraft: Story Mode is an adventure game set in 
           a Minecraft world. It is a five-part episodic series that
            will take you to the Nether, the Farlands, the End, 
            and beyond! You will drive how the story flows through
           the decisions you make: what you say to people 
            (and how you say it), and what you choose to do in
             moments of thrilling action. 9/10

        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> Mojang </name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring> Ade</starring>
        </casts>
        
        <price>‎Price € 44.99</price>
    </movie>
     <movie>
        <game>Just Cause3</game>
        <description>
            Includes 3 x exclusive vehicles primed for action:

            Knife through the Medician waves in the Mugello Delphino GLF speedboat with the finest brushed Italian leather seats and subtle dual miniguns.
            Taking its name from the Russian wolverine, exude adventure with the all-terrain Urga Pocomaxa X4 buggy, especially when that adventure requires mounted machine guns.
            For the more refined combat professional, drive the Kerner Serpente R12 sports car with precision rocket launchers elegantly engineered right into the hood.. 7/10
        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name>  Avalanche Studios</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring> Smosh</starring>
        </casts>
       
        <price>‎‎Price € 69.99</price>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <game>Rise Of The Tomb Raider</game>
        <description>
           Featuring epic, high-octane action moments set in the most 
            beautifully hostile environments on earth, Rise of the Tomb 
            Raider delivers a cinematic survival action adventure where
             you will join Lara Croft on her first tomb raiding expedition as 
            she seeks to discover the secret of immortality. 7/10

        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> Crystal Dynamics</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring>Zoe Saldana</starring>
        </casts>
       
        <price>‎Price € 69.99</price>
    </movie>
   
    <movie>
      <game>SWWE 2K16</game>
        <description>
            The authority in WWE video games returns with WWE 2K16!

          The newest addition to the flagship WWE franchise will deliver 
          authentic, high-powered and hard-hitting action, including 
          fan-favourite features and new WWE Superstars, Divas and Legends, 
          gameplay innovations, presentation updates and more. 8/10
          </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name>Youssef Chahine</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring>Youssef Chahine</starring>
            <starring>Claude Lelouch</starring>
            <starring>Samira Makhmalbaf</starring>
        </casts>
        
        <price>‎Price € 7.99</price>
    </movie>
     <movie>
        <game>Ori and the blind forest</game>
        <description>
            Ori and the Blind Forest is a single-player-only platform 
            adventure video game designed by Moon Studios, an independent 
            developer, and published by Microsoft Studios. The game was 
            released on March 11, 2015 for Microsoft Windows and Xbox One, and 
            has currently won several game awards. Highly reccomended. 10/10
        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> Moon Studios </name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring> Thomas Mahler</starring>
            <starring>Gareth Coker</starring>
            <starring>Microsoft Studios</starring>
        </casts>
      
        <price>‎‎Price € 19.99</price>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <game>Dark souls II</game>
        <description>
            Dark Souls takes place in the fictional kingdom of Lordran. 
            Players assume the role of a cursed undead character who has 
            been chosen to make a pilgrimage out of the Undead Asylum to 
            discover the fate of the Undead. The plot of Dark Souls is 
            primarily told through descriptions of in-game items and dialogue 
            with non-playable characters, and tells a chilling narrative that
            we do not wish to spoil for anyone, highly reccomended if a fan
            of rpg games. 10/10
        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name> FromSoftware</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring>Hidetaka Miyazaki</starring>
            <starring>Daisuke Uchiyamal</starring>
            <starring>Kei Hirono</starring>
        </casts>
       
        <price>‎Price € 19.99</price>
    </movie>
    <movie>
        <game>Elder scrolls V: Skyrim</game>
        <description>
           Skyrim‍ '​s main story revolves around the player character 
           and their effort to defeat Alduin the World-Eater, a dragon 
           who is prophesied to destroy the world. The game is set two 
           hundred years after the events of Oblivion and takes place in 
           the fictional province of Skyrim. Over the course of the game, 
           the player completes quests and develops the character by improving 
           skills. Skyrim continues the open world tradition of its predecessors 
           by allowing the player to travel anywhere in the game world at any 
           time, and to ignore or postpone the main storyline indefinitely. How
           you play is up to you and this is certinly the highlight of this game.
           10/10
        </description>
        <developers>
            <developer>
                <name>Bethesda Game Studios</name>
            </developer>
        </developers>
        <casts>
            <starring>Todd Howard</starring>
            <starring>Craig Lafferty</starring>
            <starring>Ashley Cheng</starring>
        </casts>
        
        <price>‎Price € 14.99</price>
    </movie>
    
</store>
